

# Sabrina Nasrin Saima

Nationality: Bangladeshi Date of birth: 20 Feb 2001 Gender: Female

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sabrina-nasrin-saima-088105247/

Github: https://github.com/S-saima

• Home: House: 02, Road: 25, Sector: 07, Uttara, Dhaka-1230, (Bangladesh)

#### **ABOUT ME**

Dedicated individual aiming to work for a well-run organization. I am efficient and well-organized with work and have level-up time management skills and have the ability to work under pressure. I have worked on several projects with both teams and individuals during my academic career. Now I am Looking forward to developing a dynamic career where I can make the best use of my skills, potentiality and hardworking through challenges.

### **ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS**

### **MSc in Computer Science**

[ Sep 2023 - Current ]

Institute: American International University-Bangladesh

# **BSc in Computer Science & Engineering (CSE)**

[ |an 2019 - |an 2023 ]

Institute: American International University-Bangladesh

**CGPA:** 3.88

Major: Software Engineering

Thesis: Earthquake Prediction in Asia Continent Using Deep Learning Methods

### **HSC** in Science

[2018]

Institute: Uttara High School & College

Board: Dhaka GPA: 4.58

## **SSC in Science**

[2016]

Institute: Uttara High School & College

Board: Dhaka GPA: 4.94

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Academic Internship**

[ 1 Sep 2022 - 30 Nov 2022 ]

Walton Hi-Tech Industries PLC.

### **Application Development Intern**

[ Feb 2023 – May 2023 ]

Genex Infosys Limited

### **PROJECTS**

### **Hotel Management System for Customer**

Web Application using PHP, Java Script, CSS & HTML

Project Link: https://github.com/S-saima/WTFinalProject

### **Online Mobile Shop Management**

Database project using Oracle

Project Link: https://github.com/S-saima/DatabaseProject

### **Automated Testing Application**

Using Selenium Software

Project Link: https://github.com/S-saima/SoftwareTesting

#### **HONOURS AND AWARDS**

#### **Achievements**

- Received **Dean's List** award in undergraduate program
- Awarded for impressive performance in the 8th Intra-AIUB Art Exhibition 2022

# **SKILLS**

## Skill Highlights

- · MySQL, Oracle
- PHP, JavaScript, CSS, HTML 5
- WordPress, Bootstrap 5
- Project & Database Management
- Basic Python
- Basic Linux
- Microsoft Office
- Good Communication

## **ACTIVITIES**

#### **Co-Curricular Activities**

Worked as an Artist at "AIUB ARTS CLUB" at AIUB

### **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

Mother tongue(s): **Bangla**Other language(s): **English** 

## **REFERENCES**

### **Associate Professor**

Name: Dr. Md. Sohidul Islam Email: sohidul@aiub.edu

American International University-Bangladesh

#### **Assistant Professor**

Name: Tohedul Islam

Email: islamtohedul@aiub.edu

American International University-Bangladesh